http://www.perx.com/privacy

Talk to a Perx expert now 1-888-737-9266Log InLog In or
RegisterChecking credentialsPlease stand by . . .The email and password are not a match.EmailPasswordForgot my password Remember meLoginCruisesResortsToursRiver CruisesGetting StartedAbout UsHomePrivacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyLast
modified: August 27, 2018Thank
you for choosing PERX.COM
At Interline Travel & Tour Inc dba Interline Vacations and Perx.com (www.perx.com),
we respect the privacy of our users and the importance of the information they
entrust to us. This Privacy Policy helps you understand what information we
collect, how we use it, and what choices you have regarding your information.When this policy mentions “PERX.COM,”
“we,” “us,” or “our” it refers to the overarching Interline Travel & Tour
Inc dba Perx.com (www.perx.com),Information
we collectThe information you provide–When you sign up for a PERX.COM account or
make a travel reservation, we ask you for personal information such as
your name, home address, email address, phone number, airline affiliation,
employment status and an account password. Cookies–When
you visit the PERX.COM website, we send one or more cookies – a small file
containing a string of characters – to your device that uniquely
identifies your browser. We use cookies to provide a secure browsing
experience and to improve the quality of our service.  The cookies we use do not personally
identify you.Log information–When
you access PERX.COM services, our servers automatically record
information that your browser sends whenever you visit the website. These
server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet
Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of
your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your
browser.User communications–When
you send email or other communications to PERX.COM, we may retain
those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your
requests and improve our services.Other sites–This
Privacy Policy applies to PERX.COM services only. We do not exercise
control over the sites displayed as links from within our various
services. These other sites will have their own privacy policies.How
we use the information collectedWe use the information we collect to
provide PERX.COM services to you.Access, Improve and Develop PERX.COM Enable you to access and use PERX.COM.Operate, protect, improve and optimize PERX.COM, such
as by performing analytics and conducting research.Provide customer service; responding to your questions
or comments.Send you service or support messages, updates and
account notifications.Operate, protect, improve, and optimize PERX.COM;  personalize and customize your experience;
conduct profiling based on your interactions with PERX.COM, search and
booking history, your profile information and preferences and other
content you submit to PERX.COM.We process this information given
our legitimate interest in improving PERX.COM and our customers’ experience
with the platforms.Personalization, Marketing and Advertising Send you promotional messages, marketing, advertising
and other information that may be of interest to you based on your
preferences.Conduct profiling on your characteristics and
preferences (based on the information you provide to us, your
interactions with PERX.COM and your search and booking history) to send
you promotional messages, marketing, advertising and other information
that we think may be of interest to you.We will process your personal
information for the purposes listed in this section given our legitimate
interest in undertaking marketing activities to offer you products or services
that may be of interest. You can opt-out of receiving marketing communications
from us by following the unsubscribe instructions included in our marketing
communications or changing your notification settings within your PERX.COM
account.Information
sharingWe will not share your personal
information with others except as indicated below:Our Affiliate Companies and agentsProperty owners and/or owner agents when a reservation
is bookedService providers, such as email service providers or
credit-card payment processors, performing services on our behalfOther third parties in limited circumstances, such as
complying with legal requirements, preventing fraud, and protecting the
safety of our usersOperating
globallyPERX.COM is a worldwide service. By
using PERX.COM, you authorize us to transfer and store your information outside
your home country, including in the United States, for the purposes described
in this policy. The privacy protections and the rights of authorities to access
your information in these countries may not be the same as in your home
country. For example, information collected within the EEA may be transferred,
stored, and processed outside of the EEA for the purposes described in this
Privacy Policy. Where we transfer, store and process your personal information
outside of the EEA we have ensured that appropriate safeguards are in place to
ensure an adequate level of data protection.Your
choices for personal informationMost browsers are initially set up
to accept cookies, but you can set your browser to refuse all cookies or to
indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some users may review or update
their personal information by logging into their accounts. If you have a PERX.COM
account, many of the choices you have on PERX.COM are built directly into PERX.COM
or your settings. For example, you can:Edit information in your profile at any time,
and decide what notifications you receive based upon watches and saved
searches.Close your account at any time. When you close your
account, we’ll deactivate it.You also have choices available to you through the
device or software you use to access PERX.COM. For example:The browser
you use allows you to control cookies or other types of local data storage. Please
note that PERX.COM features and services may not function properly if your
cookies are disabled.To learn more about these choices,
please see the information provided by your device or software provider.Other
optionsYou have options, described below,
in relation to the information that we have about you. To exercise these
options, please contact
us. If you’re user from the European Economic Area (EEA),
you can:Access the information we hold about you. We’ll usually
share this with you within 30 days of you asking us for it.Have your information corrected or deleted. You can
update your information in your settings. If you have problems updating
the information or if you would like us to delete it, contact us.Object to us processing your information. You can ask
us to stop using your information, including when we use your information
to send you marketing emails or push notifications. If you opt out of
receiving marketing messages from us, we may still send you newsletters
and updates about your account.Complain to a regulator. If you’re based in the EEA and
think that we haven’t complied with data protection laws, you have a right
to lodge a complaint with the Data Protection Commission or
with your local supervisory authority.SecurityWe take appropriate physical,
electronic and other security measures to help safeguard personal information
from unauthorized access, alteration, or disclosure.Changes
to this privacy policyPlease note that this Privacy Policy
may change from time to time. We will post any Privacy Policy changes on this
page and each version of this Privacy Policy will be identified at the top of
the page by its effective date.If you have any additional questions
or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us.×Login to find your next vacation!Checking credentialsPlease stand by . . .The email and password are not a match.EmailPasswordForgot my password Remember meLoginNot registered yet? Create your account now!Register NowNot interested in our deals? Exit here.×Privacy PolicyNo image available.No image available.No image available.No image available.Talk to a Perx expert now 1-888-737-9266Registered seller of travel: Hawaii TAR-7223 | Iowa 1338 | California 2127970-50 | Florida ST35547© 2020 Interline VacationsAbout UsPrivacy PolicyTerms & ConditionsMon to Fri - 8AM to 6PMSaturdays - 9AM to 3PMSundays - 9AM to 2PM(all times Central US)
